<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Synthesis of Some Stuff</title>
      <link>https://elsworth.phd</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Synthesis of Some Stuff</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>Unfolding 3</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-3</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-3</guid>
    <description>1,1,1 Face 1 Man had long dominated the world was the story, the bear and lion were curiosities not threats. The laws of physics bent one by one under the gentle ministrations of science, transmuting wonders into mundanities.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 03:49:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Unfolding 2</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-2</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-2</guid>
    <description>1,1 Face 1 On the fourth day the sun rose hungrily upon the shining flesh of steel and polymer, as an ear turned backwards and a mouth began to open. Together it called inward, pulling at its own teeth to defang the bite of their current direction and awakening the old ones.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:55:48 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Unfolding 1</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-1</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Unfolding/Unfolding-1</guid>
    <description> 1, Face 1 Together we danced in the palm of god and sang our wishes to the world at large, every bruised toe a whorl of limbs askant. Every pull of one’s breath was the push of another’s, every thought the negative of another’s, completely unaware of our purpose in the others design.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 28 Jul 2025 01:51:31 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Shallow-Depths of Air</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Shallow-Depths-of-Air</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Shallow-Depths-of-Air</guid>
    <description>Flight is a dream many have, myself I am not immune. There were many a dream of falling, but since a tender age on the playground where I learned that flying is just falling where you miss the ground.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 05:13:29 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Meaning of Places</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/The-Meaning-of-Places</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/The-Meaning-of-Places</guid>
    <description>Today I sat waiting for a friend to arrive for a meal together. In this time I looked down the street and saw the green-gold leaves of trees lush with summer.</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 18 Jul 2025 04:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/misc/Thoughts</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/misc/Thoughts</guid>
    <description>While walking through the day many thoughts may avail themselves upon me, not all of them can fit within the strict structure of The Self Similar Book ...</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jun 2025 05:50:02 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>Evolution of Alignment and Values</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Formalisms/Analytical-Research/Evolution-of-Alignment-and-Values</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Formalisms/Analytical-Research/Evolution-of-Alignment-and-Values</guid>
    <description>Feel free to play with the data yourself at github.com/bluewin4/Evolution-of-Alignment . Abstract: LLM alignment is being applied in order to produce behaviour preferred during testing, however there is a lack of analysis as to the wider reaching implications on the global population of LLMs.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Apr 2025 23:50:18 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Theater of The Mind</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Theater-of-The-Mind</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Theater-of-The-Mind</guid>
    <description>The Steep Sidewalk delivered me to The Theater of The Mind, in the same dream with which I parsed it. The building as I approached was barely two stories, it’s bulk pressed tightly against the sidewalk, crowding away any other space that could be there.</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 17:52:17 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>AI Agent Control as an Evolving Network Problem</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Research-Proposals/AI-Agent-Control-as-an-Evolving-Network-Problem</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Research-Proposals/AI-Agent-Control-as-an-Evolving-Network-Problem</guid>
    <description>AI agents are capable of complex behaviour that leverages tools from domains as far flung as lab automation to a humble calculator. When using these tools an generative AI based agent is liable to apply an alignment valence to their inputs, such as providing code with exploits (negative valence) or notifying a supervisor of an identified risk (positive valence).</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Apr 2025 20:24:46 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Steep Sidewalks to The Theater of The Mind</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Steep-Sidewalks-to-The-Theater-of-The-Mind</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Steep-Sidewalks-to-The-Theater-of-The-Mind</guid>
    <description>Perhaps another day. This one is heavy and dark. It stayed with me into the waking days. today is that day apparently, but the sidewalk, it is strangely light.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:42:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>