<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel>
      <title>Sythesis of Some Stuff</title>
      <link>https://elsworth.phd</link>
      <description>Last 10 notes on Sythesis of Some Stuff</description>
      <generator>Quartz -- quartz.jzhao.xyz</generator>
      <item>
    <title>The Steep Sidewalks to The Theater of The Mind</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Steep-Sidewalks-to-The-Theater-of-The-Mind</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Steep-Sidewalks-to-The-Theater-of-The-Mind</guid>
    <description>Perhaps another day. This one is heavy and dark. It stayed with me into the waking days.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:42:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Mountain&#039;s Owned by Rabbits</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Mountain's-Owned-by-Rabbits</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Mountain's-Owned-by-Rabbits</guid>
    <description>This is an unpleasant place, I do not recommend continuing to read. I might imagine The Jack King rules here, but frankly I do not know. The dream started when I was in a small compound with a couple other homes of Mediterranean style surrounded by farmland.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 22:18:44 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Keys</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/The-Keys</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/The-Keys</guid>
    <description>There are several places that can be accessed by traversing the boundaries of dreams and reality, for me. The bubblegum pink stream that sings over stones, a pathway given to me at the end of a long dream to grant me access to my dreams again.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 21:15:31 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Time Twisted Hospital and The House By The Flat Sea</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Time-Twisted-Hospital-and-The-House-By-The-Flat-Sea</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Time-Twisted-Hospital-and-The-House-By-The-Flat-Sea</guid>
    <description>I visited The House By The Flat Sea multiple times, but this time was when I appeared on the motorcycle from The Stormkissed Fields. I had known I would be there before my eyes opened fully, the fields had been replaced by sparse orchards where the ground appeared as a flat packed sandy earth with the rare stone or blemish.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 20:21:28 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Elder Forest and The Stormkissed Fields</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Elder-Forest-and-The-Stormkissed-Fields</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Elder-Forest-and-The-Stormkissed-Fields</guid>
    <description>xThis was an unexpected find for me, I had been thinking as I fell asleep of a game that was so devilishly hard that no one had ever managed to make it past the first level ...</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:36:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Sungold Villa</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Sungold-Villa</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Sungold-Villa</guid>
    <description>The villa was near the center of the peninsula of experience. For I had only ever been to the South, West, and East of the Land of Lost Hope. Perhaps it was an island, or is a continent merely a convention of the large? The villa stood atop a sturdy mountain, with plenty of space it existed within the golden hour.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 19:11:21 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Square Gardens and The Jack King</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Square-Gardens-and-The-Jack-King</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Paracosm---The-Island-of-Lost-Hope/Memories-of-My-Dreams/The-Square-Gardens-and-The-Jack-King</guid>
    <description>The square gardens are a place dripping with the verdure of spring, with flowers bursting from vibrant green grass at every possible juncture. Along the edge of the garden a darker forest looms, with a deep forest green canopy that sat atop unresolvable tree trunks; The Primordial Woods.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 18:24:09 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Particle-Bond Model of Entity Information</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/Formalisms/The-Particle-Bond-Model-of-Entity-Information</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/Formalisms/The-Particle-Bond-Model-of-Entity-Information</guid>
    <description>Entity and Particle Spaces An entity e exists as a system of causally linked particles in both physical and semantic spaces. Let us define: e = \{p_1, p_2, ..., p_n\} \cup \{s_1, s_2, ..., s_m\} Where p_i represents physical particles and s_j represents semantic particles.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 06:47:27 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Anti-suicidal Strengths of Perspectives</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/The-Anti-suicidal-Strengths-of-Perspectives</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/The-Anti-suicidal-Strengths-of-Perspectives</guid>
    <description>Each idea could be said to have a different proportion of How does religion maintain consistent long term interactions to sustain itself. So a given idea has a specific walk along an n-dimensional path of states in order to ensure that it retains “life” by ensuring it’s next step will: Each particle is performing a random walk in n-dimensions, where they trace out a space composed of both physical and semantic directions, when two nodes meet they can exchange information and continue on their walk.</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2025 04:38:01 GMT</pubDate>
  </item><item>
    <title>I have no mouth and I must Speak</title>
    <link>https://elsworth.phd/The-Self-Similar-book/I-have-no-mouth-and-I-must-Speak</link>
    <guid>https://elsworth.phd/The-Self-Similar-book/I-have-no-mouth-and-I-must-Speak</guid>
    <description>Problem Statement: Current generative AIs do not have built-in methods for communicating their internal state and may end up trapped in permanent suffering ...</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 18:48:56 GMT</pubDate>
  </item>
    </channel>
  </rss>